thanks to Unreal for sponsoring this
video this is the unreal air a pair of
AR glasses that effectively lets you
watch content from your Android or your
iPhone on a giant
130 inch screen inside of the box we
have the carrying case your typical
documentation a couple of different nose
pads a light Shield cover that can give
you a more immersive experience and a
prescription lens frame just in case you
need it but here is the unreal air
itself and it looks pretty good given
all the tech that they were able to pack
in here it's actually not too far off
from a pair of regular sunglasses which
they were clearly inspired by obviously
They are thicker but surprisingly
they're not as heavy as I thought they
would be coming in at just 79 grams now
this is in part thanks to the unreal air
not having a built-in battery with the
glasses instead being powered completely
via USBC which for Android phones is no
problem you just plug it in and it
provides both power and mirrors whatever
is on your screen whereas with iPhones
up until now this wasn't really possible
but with the new Unreal adapter they
figured it out with it working perfectly
with Apple's AV Adapter letting you
mirror whatever is on your iPhone screen
at 130 inches but the big question of
course is how does it look right like
well the thought of having a 130 inch
screen anywhere you go sounds good on
paper we've heard claims like these with
VR headsets before where it's almost
always let down since they all have that
screen door effect where all you see is
just pixels with the unreal air however
there is none of that I was actually
blown away with how sharp it is there's
two micro OLED displays with a
resolution of 3840x1080 which across the
46 degree field of view gives you over
twice the pixels per degree compared to
something like the quest 2. now I'm not
saying that it's an 8K experience or
thing but it is a 1080p experience and
for watching videos and movies it's been
great especially if you pair them with a
good set of earbuds which just takes
things to the next level of course you
don't actually have to use earbuds with
these since they do have built-in
speakers on each arm which you know are
fine for things like YouTube videos but
if you really want that home theater
Vibe using these with earbuds is
definitely the way to go now the screens
themselves provide a perceived
brightness of up to 400 nits and
generally that's more than bright enough
for example you can't even see anything
behind the screen when you have white
displaying on it but with the darker
colors you do start to become aware of
your surroundings which is kind of the
point of AR glasses and we'll talk about
the AR specific applications in a little
but if you're just wanting to use these
as a giant screen and nothing more
putting the light Shield cover on this
gives you the most vibrant experience
since it doesn't have to compete with
the lights in your environment Okay so
it's really hard to demonstrate on
camera how this thing actually looks in
person since sticking a camera up close
to it creates a bunch of Reflections
that aren't really there when you wear
them and even then the sizing is
different from what you perceive with
your eyes so just for your reference
this is what a 55 inch TV looks like
from 13 feet away which matches the
perceived distance on the unreal air and
this is how big the 130 inch screen
actually looks so just giant now in
addition to being able to watch videos
on Netflix on Hulu and YouTube and all
those other streaming apps you can also
just mirror whatever is on your phone or
computer screen since these basically
act as a monitor meaning you can work on
Excel you can use Samsung's decks you
can connect it to your M series Mac or
you can just play games on your phone
which is even better when you connect a
controller to it since these also work
with Xbox game pass so some real
opportunities to take advantage of that
giant screen but beyond just using these
as a monitor or a TV unreal also has a
mixed reality mode through their nebula
app where you're in a 3D environment
with ar native content at the moment
this only works with Android phones and
you know there isn't a huge amount of
content just yet but one of the better
examples is the cycling app where you
can simulate what it's like to be
cycling or walking through a scenic
route while you're at home and on a
treadmill and interestingly in this
mixed reality mode you can make the
screen size even bigger at 201 inches
from a perceived six feet away which is
absolutely wild but you know for me the
main use case here is using it as a
giant display on the go the air stuff is
cool and I'm sure it's going to get
better over time but just using these
around the house like when you're lying
in bed it's a game changer for example
if you're using it in bed at night you
get that big screen without blasting
light all over the room so if you have a
roommate or a partner you can actually
watch a movie without disturbing the
them while they're sleeping and on a
similar note if you're using it in
public spaces like on an airplane for
example it comes with the added benefit
of privacy where nobody else can
eavesdrop on what you're looking at on
your screen and then in those contexts
where you would otherwise be using your
phone for like a long period of time
this is a much more comfortable
experience since it's hands-free you
don't have to bend your neck down to
look at your screen and you can truly
just sit back and relax now that's not
to say that these are perfect well you
can use it as a second monitor for your
computer or for browsing the web because
we're talking about 1080p on a 130 inch
screen there is some pixelation around
text so I personally prefer using it
just for video although using it with
Samsung phones with Dex is pretty
awesome and then if you're moving around
a lot like when you're in a bumpy car
without the head tracking mode in the
nebula app like it would be with the
iPhone it could be a bit too shaky but
if you're sitting relatively still and
relaxed like on an airplane at the
doctor's office or just at home on the
couch
it's pretty good and it's easily the
best viewing experience I've had
compared to any other AR or VR headset
I've tried the unreal air comes in at
just
379 dollars which I don't think is too
bad considering it's Cutting Edge Tech
although if you have an iPhone the
unreal adapter and Apple's official AV
Adapter are sold separately you can now
buy it directly on Amazon with the
unreal error officially launching in the
US I'll be dropping all the links you
need Down Below in the description but
that's pretty much it for me in this
video big thanks to Unreal for
sponsoring it thank you guys for
watching and as always I'll see you in
the very next episode