I've been struggling to find a way to
explain what this product is how it
works and why you should potentially
keep your eye on them not because
they're bad or not interesting by any
means in fact the quite opposite this
has got to be one of the most
interesting things that I've ever had a
chance to take a look at on this YouTube
channel these unassuming glasses allow
you to achieve both in augmented reality
and virtual reality experience anywhere
you go with up to a 201 inch 1080p OLED
display it's actually kind of
unbelievable before we go further though
I do want to thank xreel for sending
these out and sponsoring this video and
allowing me to take a look at what is
now probably one of my favorite pieces
of tech that being said though and to be
clear everything in this video that I
talk about is my opinion and my opinion
alone so hit that like button subscribe
to the channel and let's get right into
it just to clear some air here no pun
intended you might have seen these
before under a different name and unreal
this is the same product and the same
brand you can trust however they've
rebranded themselves to xreel anyways I
think it's important to take a look at
these from the outside in because
there's just so much to talk about and I
don't want anyone getting lost along the
way these look like your typical pair of
sunglasses they even come with a nice
carrying case a few extra Bridge sizes a
microfiber cloth a prescription lens
frame and pretty much everything that
you'd expect from sunglasses but when
you look deeper there's a USB C to C
cable a blackout cover and wait what's
this each lens has its own display this
is where things start to get a little
funky because when you put on the xreel
air you're able to see right through
them as you would with a regular pair of
glasses but the second that you connect
them to a phone or a device like a
laptop a games console or my favorite
the steam deck you'd see it come to life
now it is quite hard to explain to you
what exactly the these look like in real
life so I'm gonna have to do my best
with showing you video through the
lenses but if there's an analogy that I
can give you that will help with this
just picture this it's like having a
floating display a few feet away from
you a very large display at that all the
way from 130 inches to 201 inches it
really does feel like the content that
you're watching is in the room in a
sense now you're probably thinking to
yourself how is this practical well
because there's head tracking and you
also have a virtual reality environment
which we'll get to there's a lot that
you can do and the possibilities with
these are kind of Limitless one way that
I've used them is while sitting at my
desk to watch TV I'm doing other things
like script writing when I want to take
a look at what's going on I turn my head
to the side catch up with what's going
on in the show look forward and just get
right back to work another example is if
you're following a recipe in the kitchen
you can watch a cooking video whilst
you're actually cooking and be able to
see what you're doing doing without a
problem and follow along just by moving
your head I like the TV example because
for me I find it very difficult to have
a ton of things going on at once so if I
put up a YouTube video while I'm on my
computer it's very hard for me to focus
because of my ADHD so being able to kind
of have it off to the side and out of
view just allows me to do two things at
once without getting too much in my head
though I will be honest I will be lying
if I said that I didn't mostly use them
with my steam deck to play some video
games there's just something about
laying on the couch putting on the
blackout cover and experiencing games
like dead cells in what quite literally
feels like a movie theater what's also
nice is that there's speakers built in
so there's no need to grab a pair of
earbuds or headphones to be able to make
this a complete experience and they do
sound really good for what they are I've
had no complaints when watching TV or
playing video games and even listening
to music through them considering how
small these drivers must be I'm actually
really happy with the sound that comes
out of them before we dive into the VR
space though there is something that I
thought was going to be an issue with
these that I ended up just being
completely wrong about and that's
Comfort when I first saw these months
ago well before xreel even reached out
to me to take a look at these I thought
that they'd be cumbersome heavy and just
not pleasing to wear at all for any
extended period of time and I'm just
happy to say that I was completely wrong
firstly these things only weigh 79 grams
and when you consider the amount of tech
inside them it's actually really
impressive one thing keeping the weight
down though is the fact that there's no
internal battery they're powered by
whichever device you're connecting to so
that's something to keep in mind as your
usage and the time that you spend
wearing them will just depend on the
battery life of whatever it's connected
to I haven't found this to be a problem
on the devices that I've used but if you
do have a phone with a less efficient
chip or just a smaller battery just be a
little bit more mindful they also stay
on my head quite well and really do just
feel like I'm wearing sunglasses is like
like it doesn't really feel like
anything's getting in the way or that
I'm wearing something that I shouldn't
which is really nice because if you do
want to wear these for an extended
period of time you just don't really
have to think about it one thing that
did help though was the three Bridge
adjustments that came inside of the
packaging I ended up actually choosing
the largest one I believe as I just felt
it was the most comfortable on my face
and I'm happy that I was given the
option something like this cannot and
should not be a one size fits all so I'm
just really happy that this is something
that they thought about there are also
physical buttons for brightness
adjustment and one to turn the screen
off and on at first I was a little
confused as to how I'm able to turn the
volume up but I realize I'm just not
very smart because you can adjust it on
whatever device is connected but not
only that it turns out there is actually
a way just by holding the brightness key
for three seconds then you are able to
change the volume through the glasses
themselves moving on though what I
really want to talk about is the
augmented reality capabilities of the
xreel air because this is where things
get mind-blowing having a large display
at your disposal is quite amazing
especially if you're traveling or want
to keep what you're watching private but
if you have a compatible smartphone you
can use the nebula app which turns your
phone into a motion controlled and touch
sensitive remote not only that but the
glasses themselves open up a whole new
world of possibilities from a
full-fledged web browser with the
ability to place multiple tabs in
different areas apps for social media
like Twitter Youtube and even games this
is called their AR space and it's
actually incredible like I said these
glasses have two 1080p OLED displays and
they're running at 60 hertz so it
essentially tricks your mind into
thinking there's actual depth between
the content and you as well as other
content or apps and windows this is
something that I really cannot
demonstrate as any screen recordings
won't show you how this looks in real
life but if you've ever used a VR
headset you know what to experience
another thing that I want to show off
quickly though is that you can use the
nebula for Mac app to get a triple
monitor setup literally anywhere via one
USBC cable that's included in the box so
if you're on a plane or away from home
for extended periods I can see these
being very practical to get actual work
done the major difference to this in
just any other VR headset though is the
portability the accessibility and the
choice between using it with the
blackout cover on or off it really feels
like you're living in this weird AR VR
smart home kind of thing and it's just
really cool all of this heavily reminds
me of something like ready player one I
just can't believe this Tech is actually
something that does exist one thing that
I've learned though with my time spent
with the xreel air is that these aren't
a gimmick and these can be really
functional in your everyday life they're
great for gaming watching movies YouTube
and a vast amount of other things it's
really up to you to best figure out how
you can utilize them anyways I hope you
all enjoyed this video thank you so much
to xreel for allowing me to make this
video and try these out to be honest I'm
kind of sad that I have to give these
back because they're a lot of fun and I
really do want to mess around with them
a little bit more but
I'll catch you in the next one peace