[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
no what is that no worries let me tell
you guys all about it although we have
so many awesome productivity tools and
applications nowaday it can easily
become overwhelming and that's precisely
the issue which accuflow is looking to
fix it literally makes me feel like I
have multiple versions of myself
the idea is to create the ultimate time
blocking platform by consolidating all
the applications that you use and let
you block time for your tasks in just
one place the Integrations I've been
loving so far have been checking my
events and reminders from Google
Calendar my assigned development issues
from jira and even checking all of my
important due dates that I have on
notion also I really love when
applications develop command palettes
akiflow did a perfect implementation of
that so you can access all the features
you need with just a few keyword
shortcuts another feature I've been
using a lot is the availability sharing
which makes scheduling meetings a breeze
so you can say goodbye to the endless
back and forth emails
so overall Accu flow is a great tool for
anyone really who is looking to take
control of their time and boost your
productivity try it out today and see
for yourself thank you accuflow for
being a partner on this channel let's
get back to the video
all right so let's just get straight
into it and I'll start by showing you my
development environment which I just use
Visual Studio code and for the most part
I think I keep it pretty simple just
have a couple extensions that help with
formatting and a lot of language support
ones as well then for the terminal I
just use the integrated terminal most of
the time I just find it more convenient
to have there as opposed to opening up a
separate window so when I don't use the
integrated terminal with MBS code I use
item with power level 10K which is a zsh
theme do like that it shows cool things
like get and autocomplete on here
another tool that I use almost daily now
in vs code is GitHub co-pilot and I had
tried out the beta actually some time
back but then I was disappointed to
learn that it became a paid service but
for about 10 bucks a month I think it's
pretty hard to beat let me show you a
quick example of what you can do with
GitHub co-pilot
it usually just takes the context from a
comment or it looks at the code you had
previously written
and there you go look at how fast it
comes up with the solution
and that brings me to the next tool
which I've been using so much which is
chat GPT if you're not familiar it's an
artificial intelligence language model
that's been trained to answer all sorts
of questions from Tech related topics to
even personal advice it's able to
understand natural language and generate
responses that sounds like they were
written by human I've been using it for
so many things like writing and
responding to emails
coding project setups and system design
and even smaller things like asking it
for simple front-end design kind of
questions
actually pretty amazing stuff I even
added a cool new shortcut to use the
chat GPT Pro from any of my Apple
devices hey Siri run chat GPT shortcut
how to start a next JS project using
typescript
on it
xjs project using typescript you can
follow these steps one create a new
next.js next is notion which is actually
one of my favorite tools at the moment
is like an all-in-one workspace Way
Beyond note taking which lets you do so
many cool things the way I've been using
notion is to keep track of all of my
development notes
for meetings such as stand-ups epic team
meetings and Sprint planning and keeping
a work log of all of my weekly issues
and I've been using notion for Beyond
software development I even keep track
of my clients for my site photography
business
and even to manage my YouTube videos
that I've been planning out so the next
food that I've been using is figma figma
is a powerful design tool that allows me
to create and collaborate on user
interface and other design assets I
appreciate the ability to work with my
team in real time and collaborate on
things like Design Systems prototyping
and creating mockups figma has really
accelerated my workflow as a full stack
engineer since you have to work pretty
quickly sometimes and figma has been
more than just web design for me I even
use it to manage all of my YouTube
content from things like thumbnails
Graphics to captions and titles and so
much more really I would encourage
anyone to pick up on figma even if
you're not working with web development
it's really an all-in-one tool for
anything design related
the bonus two I'm going to throw in is
the arc browser Arc is a new browser
which looks to improve and restructure
the way browsers are laid out I feel
like the arc browser gives me the clean
feel of safari with their power features
of chrome like extensions and chrome
developer tools which I always have open
when I'm doing web development Mark also
has a pretty neat onboarding which
leaves you with a cool custom sticker at
the end but it's still in development
and I don't think it's publicly
available yet here's a code if you want
to try it out
last but not least I want to mention
Excalibur which is an open source
web-based tool that allows you to create
diagrams and other visual assets quickly
and easily I used it a lot back when I
was on the Lee code grind as a
whiteboarding tool to help sketch out
and solve data structure and algorithm
problems so there you have it those were
just a few of my favorite and kind of
General tools that help me as a software
developer whether you're an experienced
developer or just starting out there's
always cool new things to learn oh and
let me know down in the comments if you
have any other tools you'd recommend for
me to try out
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
so much
all right so around this time of the
year we do go watch our siblings play
high school soccer but today actually
may be the very last time my brother
plays at home because he's a senior he's
graduating
um so we'll see how they do see you over
there
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
thank you
[Music]