[-效力FLIPPED (2010)]
[strategic-战略 avoidance and social discomfort-不适.]
[I was about to tell her to get lost, when the weirdest-怪异的 thing happened.]
[School would not be a sanctuary-避难所.]
[To full appreciate, the brilliance-卓越 of this plan...]
[My only consolation-安慰, was that next year would be different.]
[The first day I met Bryce Loski, I flipped. -女方称述]
[I would give him plenty-丰富, of opportunity to get over his shyness-害羞.]
[All hair and no substance-实质.]
[a shallow-肤浅 conniver-纵容 like Sherry Stalls.]
[It took all of a week., They broke up at recess-休假.]
[Seventh grade brought changes, all right. -男方陈述]
[She always thought it was God's gift, to our little corner of the universe-宇宙.]
[I'd be dragged-拖着 right back, into the second grade.]
[You're just visually-审美 challenged., I feel sorry for you.]
[It -窃听 my dad bigtime.]
[The bricklayer-砌墙工人 who thinks he's a painter., That truck's not ugly enough in real life?]
[No, he does landscapes-风景., Sells them at the county fair-市集.]
[You are trespassing-非法入侵 and obstructing-妨碍, progress on a contracted-约定的 job.]
[I couldn't understand why, that mutant-突变 tangle-缠绕 of gnarly-粗糙的 branches...]
[That girl has an iron backbone-志气.]
[And she's been stalking-围捕 me, since the second grade.]
[I see why you like to come out here. -女方陈述]
[- What?, - You have to look at the whole landscape-风景.]
[I was rescuing-营救 a kite-风筝.]
[I can't. I sprained-扭伤 my, um...]
[I have a rash-皮症.]
[From that moment on,, that became my spot-地点.]
[What happened after that was a blur-模糊.]
[of a rhomboid-菱形.]
[Somehow, rhomboids, and isosceles-等腰 right triangles-三角形...]
[most magnificent-宏伟的 sycamore tree.]
[I've never been a huge fan of eggs. -男方陈述]
[were solidified-固化的.]
[So, Brycie, how do you think, he's gonna digest-消化 that?]
[and start to devour-吞 me.]
[Then the real nightmare-噩梦 began.]
[You remember Abby and Bonnie and Clyde, and Dexter and Eunice and Florence? -五只鸡]
[She totally dominated-统治地位 the fair.]
[I mean, here I had a live-action, erupting-爆发 volcano火山...]
[was Juli's boring chicks-小鸡...]
[Do they have a rooster-公鸡? If they don't, have a rooster the eggs can't be fertile-受精.]
[- Well, a rooster's bigger. Longer feathers-翅膀., - Mm-hm.]
[See what I mean? Expertise-专门技术.]
[- Roosters strut-至高气傲的走?, - Come on, guys.]
[There's not even any grass., It's all mud-泥  and chicken turds.]
[Uh, we're allergic-过敏 to them or something.]
[with lies, intrigue-阴谋 and deception.]
[Now, you wanna make sure you get it... -女方陈述]
[But I begged and pleaded-恳求.]
[Between Mrs. Steuby and Mrs. Helms,, my egg overflow-溢出 problem was solved.]
[Then I realized that Mrs. Loski, deserved-理所应当  eggs too.]
[It was a bargain-交易.]
[Yeah, well, neither rain nor sleet-雨夹雪.]
[It didn't take me long to realize... -男方陈述]
[Don't be so timid-胆小的., Come on, you won't hurt them.]
[All I ever saw him wear was slippers-拖鞋., Now, where did he get those work boots-靴子?]
[When it came to holding a grudge-怨恨,, Juli Baker was truly impressive-印象深刻.]
[All week I tried to approach-接近 her, at school.]
[She'd always find some way to duck-闪避 me.]
[I don't know. It was dumb-哑的.]
[But he meant it in a nice way., Something about her spirit-性格.]
[While Juli's acceptance-接受 of, my apology was not all that I'd hoped for...]
[That's ridiculous-可笑的.]
[Yeah, because he's too busy, with his paint-by-numbers kit-工具.]
[If you had a brother with a sever-严重的 handicap-障碍,, what would you do?]
[What the hell-地狱, does that have to do with anything?]
[Juli's father has a retarded-智力上迟钝的 brother.]
[So what? He's not the gardener-花匠,, is he? Heh.]
[to mow their own lawns-草地.]
[I don't know where their pride-骄傲, in ownership is.]
[The landlord's-房东 supposed to maintain-维修 it.]
[Mr. Baker puts every extra penny-便士 he has, into caring for his brother.]
[Don't they have government facilities-设施, for that sort of thing?]
[Maybe they thought that a private facility-容易, would be better for him.]
[Either way, it's not our fault that their, family has some chromosomal-染色体 abnormality-异常.]
[When Juli's uncle was born, he had, the umbilical-脐带 cord-束缚 wrapped around his neck.]
[Why is Mom so upset-心烦?]
[Luckily, the doctor who delivered-原型 you, was on the ball and got it untangled...-解开]
[You can't dwell-存在 on something, that might've been, Bryce.]
[The way my dad was talking, sounds like, he would've thrown me in a nuthouse-精神病院.]
[You can't condemn-谴责 him, for something he hasn't done.]
[Must've been a spectacular-壮观的 view.]
[Some of us get dipped-浸 in flat-平坦的...]
[Flat, glossy-平滑的, iridescent?]
[Juli Baker had always, just seemed plain-平原 to me.]
[Who in junior-年少 high talks like that?]
[This weird-怪异 feeling started taking over, in the pit of my stomach...]
[I was slipping-滑动, man.]
[I'd never been embarrassed, by where we lived before. -女方陈述]
[With charms-吸引力 like yours for me]
[We'll record it in Skyler's garage-车库.]
[I could even put up a fence-围墙.]
[Honey, that's a major undertaking-事业.]
[I'm tired of having to take temp jobs, just to make ends meet-集会.]
[I'm tired of having to borrow, Mrs. Steuby's vacuum-真空 cleaner...]
[Sometimes you have to sacrifice-牺牲, to do the right thing.]
[We always end up agreeing that Devonhurst, is the right thing for 丹尼尔.]
[Our daughter is suffering-苦难, because we won't fix up our own yard.]
[That was the first time I ever heard, my parents really yell-叫喊 at each other.]
[many blessing-祝福, I was her best.]
[Are you pruning-修建 that, or trying to hack-劈 it to death?]
[So are you trimming-整理 all these, to the same height?]
[Oh, these are Hicksii shrubs-灌木., These will prune-修建 up nicely.]
[I started looking at people, I'd known since elementary-基础 school...]
[that Bryce Loski was less-少的.]
[We're going to invite the Bakers -男方陈述, over for dinner.]
[I think that's a marvelous-令人惊讶的 idea.]
[The statute-法规 of limitations-局限性 has run out.]
[And I expect everyone, to dress accordingly-相应.]
[Oh, God. Can't we just have a barbecue-烤肉?]
[If I didn't do something fast,, this could spread like wildfire-野火.]
[I convinced-确信 myself I'd dodged-闪躲 a bullet.]
[Keep the focus on the important stuff-东西, like schoolwork.]
[My weakness-弱点 was unnerving-令人不安的.]
[I need your sharpener-卷笔刀.]
[- Or should I say your best? Ha, ha., - You're disgusting-讨厌的.]
[Another disaster-不幸 avoided.]
[My life had become a minefield-布雷区.]
[Garrett was surprisingly-是人惊奇的 sensitive, in matters-事态 of the heart.]
[Are you freaking-糟糕 mental-心理? Juli Baker., You hate her.]
[That's what's weird-怪异的. I don't think I do., I can't stop thinking about her.]
[Well, you gotta nip this in the bud-现在., These aren't real emotions.]
[Yeah, and I insulted-侮辱 her yard.]
[Exactly. Of course,, the place is a dump-垃圾场 anyways.]
[I couldn't believe it., I wanted to yell-争辩 at him.]
[Sunday mornings, are peaceful in our house. -女方陈述]
[If my brothers have been out late, playing with their band... -饭间交谈]
[But this Sunday, I woke up feeling weird. - 女方描述]
[- Where you going?, - To see 丹尼尔. It's his birthday.]
[Sometimes, with 丹尼尔...]
[In all the years,, I'd never visited my Uncle 丹尼尔.]
[Somehow the silence-沉默 seemed to connect us, in a way that words never could.]
[The residents-住院医生 tend to the grounds, as part of their therapy-治疗.]
[Your niece-侄女.]
[- Ha, Julianna., - Happy birthday, Uncle 丹尼尔.]
[A puzzle-拼图? A puzzle, Richard?]
[- All right, 丹尼尔. Okay, wait, wait., - Ice cream. Ice cream.]
[- My ice cream. My ice cream. Ugh!, - It's okay. 丹尼尔.]
[I'd often heard my father talk about, how difficult life was for 丹尼尔.]
[On the ride home,, my dad told me that Uncle 丹尼尔...]
[Before today, 丹尼尔 had always been, just a name to me.]
[Trina, it's Sunday., What are you doing mopping-拖把 the floor?]
[Nervous energy-精力.]
[Well, she insisted-坚决.]
[I wasn't too thrilled-激动 about dinner, with the Loskis...]
[At school the next day,, I couldn't seem to concentrate-浓缩.]
[My thoughts kept running back to 丹尼尔.]
[He's got a big crush-迷恋 on you.]
[Is that the lamest-差劲 cover-up or what?]
[I saw him sneaking-暗中 off with Garrett., Come on.]
[Because now my confusion-混乱 was gone.]
[Mom, are you trying to make the Bakers, feel totally worthless-无价值的? -南方陈述]
[- Come in, come in., - There goes the waistline-腰围.]
[I'm glad you could make it., Lynetta, 史蒂文, company's here.]
[- Coming!, - What is this? Homemade-自制的 pie?]
[Yes, it's pecan- 美洲山核桃, and blueberry-乌饭树 cheesecake-干烙饼.]
[Hey, 史蒂文. How are you?]
[- And I say you can., - But what you're proposing...-提议]
[If you had two opposite-相反的 charged-强烈的 poles-两极, with a neutral-中立 conductor-领导者...]
[Then that makes you a coward-胆小的人.]
[We should have barbecued-烧烤.]
[We are just all so thrilled-兴奋的 to be here.]
[- 史蒂文., - I kid-开玩笑.]
[I mean, that new house is taking shape-形状.]
[Some people thought that tree, was the jewel-珠宝 of the neighborhood.]
[Yeah, well,, there's no accounting-账单 for taste.]
[You guys are, uh, gonna be, graduating-毕业 soon, huh?]
[- Really?, - Oh, they are very talented-才能.]
[When 史蒂文 and I first met,, he was playing in a band.]
[He was a wonderful saxophone-沙克斯 player.]
[The more Matt and Mark, talked about their musical exploits-漏洞利用...]
[He tried to plaster-掩饰 on a smile, now and then...]
[Republicans-共和党 fought like crazy, against the New Deal.]
[Her apology-道歉 made things worse.]
[It was like I wasn't even important enough, to hold a grudge-怨恨 against.]
[Well, I think they're a delightful-令人愉快 family.]
[- Hoodlums-流氓., - What?]
[How you think they can afford, all that recording-记录 gear-工具?]
[You can't just make an accusation-指则 like that.]
[They're probably stealing hubcaps-轮毂罩,, for chrissake-圣诞礼物.]
[You are such an asshole-混蛋.]
[And how he'd called them trash-垃圾, and made fun of Mr. Baker's paintings.]
[Or, more accurately-正确的...]
[As I was getting dressed, for the Loskis' dinner party... -女方陈述]
[At dinner it struck-罢工 me that we were sharing, a meal with a group of strangers.]
[Mr. Loski was clean and smooth-和蔼的, on the outside...]
[rotten-腐烂的 buried-埋葬 just beneath the surface-表面.]
[By the end of the evening,, all I felt was detached-冷淡的, neutral-中立的.]
[No fireworks-争论, no leftover-遗留 anger...]
[I went to bed that night feeling peaceful-平静的.]
[The dinner with the Bakers, had taken its toll on me. -男方陈述]
[Then the annual-每年的, school fundraiser-资金筹集 arrived... - 南方视角]
[To fully appreciate the humiliation-丢脸, of being a Basketboy...]
[auctioned-拍卖 off in front of the student body...]
[Yes, technically-技术上, each of us, comes with a lunch in a basket...]
[This was a beefcake parade-游行.]
[She and Melanie, are having a bidding-招标 war over you.]
[Are you nuts-发狂?, Sherry dumped-分手 Mitch because of you.]
[As comforting-安慰 as it was, to be Garrett's idol...]
[And my only hope was that a giant-巨大 tornado-旋风, would destroy the school before the event.]
[Once again we are pleased to present-礼品...]
[- So?, - So she's got a wad-一卷 of cash.]
[I saw her counting it by her locker-抽屉.]
[Was it possible, she was gonna bid-出价 on me?]
[the handsome-英俊 Mr. Hughes...]
[Oh. Excuse me, onion dip-吃的.]
[Eddie is a member of the debate-辩论 team.]
[Now only Eddie Trulock, stood-过去 between me and the auction block.]
[I was contemplating-深思 the horrors-恐怖, of this when...]
[Here I was, having lunch, with the hottest-火辣 girl in school...]
[We're going up to the lake-湖., My dad has a cabin-小屋 there...]
[Can we not talk about tans-晒黑 or food?]
[I don't know, perpetual-永动机 motion?, Do you know anything about that?]
[I don't know what came over me., It was like I was possessed-中魔 or something.]
[You get a date with the finest-最杰出 girl, on campus-校园 and you blow-打击 it for Juli.]
[Nightmare-噩梦 neighbor, know-it-all nuisance-讨厌的东西., The coop-poop babe-小孩.]
[You know what, if you're gonna be like this,, I don't need the association-联想.]
[As I walked home with the dirty, dishes-餐具 clanking-发出叮当声 inside my picnic basket...]
[Monday morning,, as I made my way into school... -女方称述]
[Because rumor-谣言 has it Sherry's, already staking her claim-要求 on him.]
[That afternoon, I found myself, obsessing-缠住 about the Basketboy auction.]
[I could feel myself backsliding-倒退, about Bryce.]
[On the morning of the auction,, I was on edge-边缘.]
[I needed a strategy-战略.]
[If I left my money at home,, I'd leave temptation-诱惑 with it.]
[My strategy suffered a setback-挫折, when I ran into Mrs. Steuby.]
[Don't be ridiculous-可笑. I'm gonna pay you.]
[Yeah, I want you to go out, and buy yourself something festive-欢乐的.]
[- Mrs. Steuby, I don't want pedal-脚的 pushers-咄咄逼人., - No, no. You'll look great.]
[It's okay. No big deal., Just pretend-假装 like I don't have it.]
[the startling-令人吃惊的 turn of events.]
[with my mortal-人类的 enemy-敌军.]
[- I hear you like building model airplanes-飞机., - Yeah.]
[MiG's first supersonic-超声波 fighter., Tricky because the cockpit-驾驶舱 was recessed-嵌入式...]
[Eddie was saying something, about intake-进气 valves-阀门...]
[and marched-前进 straight towards me.]
[I pedaled-踩自行车的踏板 home so hard,, I thought my lungs-肺 would burst-破裂.]
[He even snuck-潜行 around the house, and tapped-轻拍 on my window.]
[Permission? Permission for what?, He's digging-挖掘 a hole.]
[It was torture-折磨 seeing him, dig up my grass-草地.]
[The scene-场景 where we're doing, the Basketboy thing...]
[You gotta be serious about this., You can't be giggling-咯咯笑 during this.]
[And he grabs-抢 me and he goes like:]
[That was really fun to film, but it was really awkward-笨拙的 as well.]
[My face drained-累极了. I'm just like:]